[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I'm wary of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I'm holding it, I'm holding it.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is Sri Lankan crate.
[SPEAKER_01]: You saw an Indian crate.
[SPEAKER_01]: They tend to be bigger.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to be gentle, because they're not very... scales are sort of... that's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, what happens with this one if it bites you?
[SPEAKER_01]: There is an antivenom, but it can cause organ damage, even if you get antivenom.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you don't really want to be bitten by... Oops!
[SPEAKER_01]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, it is beautiful.
[SPEAKER_00]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Outside of our fence, because I don't want it to get... Well, injure the dogs or gets injured by the dogs.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I got masked by a crate and it really stinks.
[SPEAKER_01]: My goodness, when I grabbed it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's worse than a rat snake, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Watch out for more crates.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gone.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's still, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really bad stink.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, you washed your hands with that soapy, flowery soap.
[SPEAKER_00]: I did.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to do it again.
[SPEAKER_01]: I need something stronger.
[SPEAKER_00]: It just smells like...
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, smells like insides, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Feces with... Feces with everything else imaginable.
[SPEAKER_01]: Flowers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you have something stronger?
[SPEAKER_00]: That is the strongest.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, maybe I'll try this one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's not this bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is quite potent.
[SPEAKER_01]: You often wouldn't necessarily even feel the bite of the crate, but the teeth are actually like maybe a millimeter or so tiny.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like a lizard.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, yeah, I think so, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think those lizards might have bigger teeth than, than, uh, great fangs.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's, um, it's a neurotoxin.
[SPEAKER_01]: You stop breathing.
[SPEAKER_00]: And your organs start shutting down.